Guide to the Fantasy Magazine Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1931-79; Series I; 1.75; (4 boxes)
  - Roberts, Lynnette, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 176)
  - Robson, William N., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 177)
  - Rocky Mountain Review
    See: George D. Snell, Box 4 folder 192
  - Rosenberger, Coleman, 1939-43 (Box 3, Folder 178)
  - Roskolenko, Harry, 1935-70, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 179)
  - Rosten, Norman, 1943, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 180)
  - Ryan, John J., 1931, 1933 (Box 3, Folder 180)
  - "S" general, 1933-79, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 181)
  - Salinger, Herman, 1939-69 (Box 3, Folder 182)
  - Sarett, Lew, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 183)
  - Satterthwaite, Arnold, 1942-43 (Box 3, Folder 184)
  - Schmidt, Alex R., 1935-41 (Box 3, Folder 185)
  - Schorer, Mark, 1935, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 186)
  - Scott, Virginia, 1935-38 (Box 4, Folder 186)
  - Scott, Winfield Townley, 1936-41, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 187)
  - Seymour, George Steele, 1935, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 188)
  - Shand, William, 1941, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 189)
  - Shefler, Oscar, 1940-68, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 190)
  - Silhouettes
    See: James Neill Northe, Box 3 folder 159
  - Simpson, Claude M., Jr., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 191)
  - Smythe, Daniel W., 1935, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 191)
  - Snell, George D., 1935-43 (Box 4, Folder 192)
  - Sparks, William Sheppard, 1934-42, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 193)
  - Spears, Woodridge, 1937-40 (Box 4, Folder 194)
  - Spier, Leonard, 1933 (Box 4, Folder 195)
  - Spivak, Lawrence, 1935, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 195)
  - Stark, Irwin, 1942-43 (Box 4, Folder 196)
  - Stephens, Pauline Francis, 1933 (Box 4, Folder 197)
  - Steward, S. M., 1936 (Box 4, Folder 198)
  - Still, James, 1936-40 (Box 4, Folder 199)
  - Stuart, Jesse, 1941, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 200)
  - Sutton, Harry Trumbull, 1935-36 (Box 4, Folder 201)
  - Sutton, Kathleen, 1935-40 (Box 4, Folder 201)
  - Swallow, Allan, 1941-43, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 202)
  - Sweeney, Thomas Bell, 1933-36 (Box 4, Folder 203)
  - "T" general, 1935-43, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 204)
  - Tawnley, Eleanor, 1937-43, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 205)
  - Temple, Jean, 1935-36 (Box 4, Folder 206)
  - Terry, T. Philip, 1942-43 (Box 4, Folder 207)
  - Townsman, A Quarterly
    See: Ronald Duncan, Box 1 folder 61
  - Treece, Henry, 1939, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 208)
  - Troubadour
    See: Grace K. Wellington, Box 4 folder 225
  - Trowbridge, W. D., n.d. (Box 4, Folder 209)
  - Twice A Year
    See: Dorothy Norman, Box 3 folder 158
  - Twynham, Leonard, 1937-39, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 210)
  - Tyler, Parker, 1935-43, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 211)
  - "U" general, 1939-43, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 212)
  - Uhlarik, Carl, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 213)
  - United States. Dept. of State Division of Cultural Relations, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 214)
  - United States. Office for Emergency Management. Coordinator of Inter-American Affairs, 1941-42 (Box 4, Folder 215)
  - Urquhart, Fred, 1941-43 (Box 4, Folder 216)
  - Uzzell, Thomas H., 1933-41 (Box 4, Folder 217)
  - "V" general, 1940-43 (Box 4, Folder 218)
  - Valentine, Louis, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 219)
  - Van Brunt, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 220)
  - View
    See: Charles Henri Ford, Box 2 folder 75
  - Vinal, Harold, 1933-41 (Box 4, Folder 221)
  - "W" general, 1938-43, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 222)
  - Waller, John, 1938, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 223)
  - Warp and Woof
  - Weismiller, Edward, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 224)
  - Wellington, Grace K., 1932-47, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 225)
  - Wermuth, A. F., 1942-43 (Box 4, Folder 226)
  - West, Jessamyn McPherson, 1940, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 227)
  - Wetstein, Aleen, 1932 (Box 4, Folder 228)
  - Wheelock, John Hall, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 229)
  - Wheelwright, John, 1939, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 230)
  - Wicker, C. V., n.d. (Box 4, Folder 231)
  - Wicker, Mary, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 231)
  - Williams, Oscar, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 232)
  - Williams, William Carlos, 1935 (Box 4, Folder 233)
  - Wings: A Literary Quarterly
    See: Stanton Coblentz, Box 1 folder 39
  - Winslow, Kathryn, 1935-36, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 234)
  - Winslow, Walker, 1935, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 234)
  - Wood, Clement, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 235)
  - Woods, Bertha Gernaux, 1935-36, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 236)
  - "Y" general, 1936-43, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 237)
  - Zaturenska, Marya, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 238)
  - Ziron, M. C., 1934 (Box 4, Folder 239)
  - Zugsmith, Leane, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 240)
  - Unidentified, 1932-68, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 241)
- Manuscript Submissions, 1931-43; Series II; 1.25; (3 boxes)
  Series II is arranged alphabetically by name of contributor, then chronologically within each folder. Undated material is placed at the end of the folders. Unidentified manuscripts are found in a separate folder at the end of the series.
  - Abbe, George, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 242)
  - Aguirre, Manuel Agustin, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 243)
  - Allison, Brent, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 244)
  - Anderson, J. Redwood (Box 5, Folder 245)
  - Anguita, Eduardo, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 246)
  - Bartra, Agusti, 1939, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 247)
  - Bennett, William H., n.d. (Box 5, Folder 248)
  - Benton, Walter, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 249)
  - Bernstein, Walter, 1935 (Box 5, Folder 250)
  - Blanding, Don, 1935 (Box 5, Folder 251)
  - Bonet, Carmelo M., n.d. (Box 5, Folder 252)
  - Bragdon, Clifford, 1933, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 253)
  - Bramlett, William, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 254)
  - Brassert, Janet, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 255)
  - Breit, Harvey, 1938, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 256)
  - Brown, Leonard, 1939, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 257)
  - Burkland, Carl Edwin (Box 5, Folder 258)
  - Bynner, Witter, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 259)
  - Calamaro, Eduardo, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 260)
  - Caldiero, F. St. M., n.d. (Box 5, Folder 261)
  - Cheyney, Ralph, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 262)
  - Coblentz, Stanton, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 263-64)
  - Coffin, Robert P. Tristam, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 265)
  - Comfort, Alex, 1942-[43], n.d. (Box 5, Folder 266-67)
  - Conroy, Jack, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 268)
  - [Crouch, W. George], [1937-38?] (Box 5, Folder 269)
  - Cuney, Waring, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 270)
  - Davidman, Joy, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 271)
  - Davis, Franklin Marshall, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 272)
  - Decker, Duane, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 273)
  - DeLong, David C., n.d. (Box 5, Folder 274)
  - Derleth, August, 1937-41, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 275-76)
  - Dixon, Evalyn, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 277)
  - D'Lettuso, Homer, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 278)
  - D'Nova, 1933-37, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 279)
  - DuBois, Arthur E., [1937?], n.d. (Box 5, Folder 280-81)
  - Dudgeon, Patrick O., [1941?], n.d. (Box 5, Folder 282)
  - Duncan, Ronald, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 283)
  - Duncan, Thomas W., n.d. (Box 5, Folder 284)
  - Eaton, Charles Edward, 1940, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 285)
  - Eberhart, Richard, 1941-42 (Box 5, Folder 286)
  - Eluard, Paul, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 287)
  - Farbstein, W. E., n.d. (Box 5, Folder 288)
  - Farrell, James T., n.d. (Box 5, Folder 289)
  - Faust, George, 1935, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 290)
  - Fenderson, Lewis H. (Box 5, Folder 291)
  - Field, Sara Bard, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 292)
  - Florit, Eugenio, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 293)
  - [Foka, A.?], n.d. (Box 5, Folder 294)
  - Fombona-Pachano, Jacinto, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 295)
  - Foote, Alvin, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 296)
  - Ford, Charles Henri, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 297)
  - Forkin, Katherine, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 298)
  - Friedrich, Ralph, 1940, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 299)
  - Garcia Lorca, Federico
    See: Lloyd Mallan, Box 6, folder 344
  - Gessler, Clifford, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 300)
  - Glicksberg, Charles, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 301-02)
  - Graber, Edwin C., [1939] (Box 5, Folder 303)
  - Grucci, Joseph Leonard, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 304)
  - Guillén, Nicolás, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 305)
    See also: Langston Hughes, Box 6 folder 316
  - Gustafson, Ralph, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 306)
  - Haddad, Jamil Almansur, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 307)
  - Hamilton, Anne, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 308)
  - Hargan, James, [1938?] (Box 6, Folder 309)
  - Hatcher, Harlan, 1936 (Box 6, Folder 310)
  - Hays, H. R., n.d. (Box 6, Folder 311)
  - Heywood, Terence, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 312)
  - Higgins, James, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 313)
  - Hofrichter, Ruth J., n.d. (Box 6, Folder 314)
  - Hudeburg, Charles, 1936 (Box 6, Folder 315)
  - Hughes, Langston, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 316)
  - Huidobro, Vicente, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 317)
  - Hunter, J. Stewart, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 318)
  - Isaacs, Leo, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 319)
  - Jimenez, Hernandez (Box 6, Folder 320)
  - Johnson, Josephine W., n.d. (Box 6, Folder 321)
  - Jolas, Eugene, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 322)
  - Jones, Putnam Fennell, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 323)
  - Jones, Willis Knapp, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 324)
  - Kees, Weldon, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 325)
  - Kelm, Karlton, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 326)
  - Kozlenko, William, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 327)
  - Kresensky, Raymond (Box 6, Folder 328)
  - Lampson, Robin, 1935-38, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 329)
  - Laughlin, James, 1936, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 330)
  - Lehman, Milton, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 331)
  - LeSeur, Meridel, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 332)
  - Lewis, E. E., n.d. (Box 6, Folder 333)
  - Lewis, James Franklin, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 334)
  - Lieberman, Elias, 1936 (Box 6, Folder 335)
  - Litsey, Edwin Carlile, 1934, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 336)
  - Lodge, Evan, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 337)
  - Loggins, Vernon, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 338)
  - Long, Haniel, 1936-38, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 339)
  - López, Luis Carlos, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 340)
  - López Velarde, Ramón, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 341)
  - McCarthy, John Russell, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 342)
  - MacLeod, Norman, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 343)
  - Mallan, Lloyd, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 344)
  - Mallea, Eduardo, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 345)
  - Manch, Joseph Rodman, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 346)
  - Mangan, Sherry, 1937 (Box 6, Folder 347)
  - Manning, Hugo, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 348)
  - Markham, Edwin, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 349)
  - Masters, Edgar Lee, 1936, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 350)
  - Meeter, George F., n.d. (Box 6, Folder 351)
  - Mendez Calzada, Enrique (Box 6, Folder 352)
  - Merriam, Eve, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 353)
  - Miller, Fred R., n.d. (Box 6, Folder 354)
  - Mills, Clark, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 355)
  - Mitchell, Ruth Hill, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 356)
  - Moody, Minnie Hite, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 357)
  - Moore, Nicolas, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 358)
  - Morang, Alfred, 1935, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 359)
  - Morgenstern, Christian, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 360)
  - Mullins, Helene, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 361)
  - Musser, Ben, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 362)
  - Neagoe, Peter, 1936 (Box 6, Folder 363)
  - Neider, Charles, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 364)
  - Nemerov, Howard, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 365)
  - Neruda, Pablo, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 366)
    See also: Leonard Joseph Grucci, Box 5 folder 304
  - Nieman, Gilbert, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 367)
  - Nutt, Howard, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 368)
  - Otero Silva, Miguel, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 369)
  - Panetta, George, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 370)
  - Paquette, Donald J., n.d. (Box 7, Folder 371)
  - Patchen, Kenneth, 1936-38, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 372)
  - Pauker, John, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 373)
  - Paz, Octavio
    See: Leonard Joseph Grucci, Box 5 folder 304
  - Pedroso, Regino, 1941-42 (Box 7, Folder 374)
  - Peterson, Edwin L., n.d. (Box 7, Folder 375)
  - Pichardo Moya, Felipe, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 376)
  - Pierce, Rosamon F., [1935?] (Box 7, Folder 377)
  - Pillin, William, 1938, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 378)
  - Posner, Harry
    See: D'Nova, Box 5, folder 279
  - Pudney, John, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 379)
  - Quinn, Kerker, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 380)
  - Rahv, Philip, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 381)
  - Re, Arundell del, 1936-39 (Box 7, Folder 381)
  - Rexroth, Kenneth, [1940?] (Box 7, Folder 382)
  - Rhys, Keidrych, 1938-39 (Box 7, Folder 383)
  - Ridge, Lola, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 384)
  - Roberts, Lynnete, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 385)
  - Rokha, Pablo de, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 385)
  - Root, E. Merrill, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 386)
  - Rosenberger, Coleman, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 387)
  - Roskolenko, Harry, 1934-42 (Box 7, Folder 388)
  - Rosten, Norman, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 389)
  - Ryan, John J., [1931-32], n.d. (Box 7, Folder 390)
  - Salinger, Herman, 1939-42, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 391)
  - Salinger, Marion C., n.d. (Box 7, Folder 392)
  - Schmitt, Gladys, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 393)
  - Schorer, Mark, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 394)
  - Scollard, Clinton, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 395)
  - Scott, Winfield Townley, 1938-39, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 396)
  - Shand, William (Box 7, Folder 397)
  - Smythe, Daniel W., n.d. (Box 7, Folder 398)
  - Snell, George D., n.d. (Box 7, Folder 399)
  - Spier, Leonard, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 400)
  - Stegner, Wallace, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 401)
  - Steinhauer, H., n.d. (Box 7, Folder 402)
  - Still, James, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 403)
  - Stuart, Jesse, 1935, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 404)
  - Temple, Jean, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 405)
  - Thomas, Dylan, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 406)
  - Torres Rioseco, Arturo, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 407)
  - Treece, Henry, 1939-40 (Box 7, Folder 408)
  - Trent, Lucia, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 409)
  - Trowbridge, W. D., n.d. (Box 7, Folder 410)
  - Twynham, Leonard, 1937, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 411)
  - Tyler, Parker, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 412)
  - Umphrey, George W., n.d. (Box 7, Folder 413)
  - Unávez, Nicolas, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 414)
  - Urquhart, Fred, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 415)
  - Vazakas, Byron, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 416)
  - Villaurrutia, Xavier, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 417)
  - Vinal, Harold, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 418)
  - Voorhees, Edward Lloyd, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 419)
  - Waller, John, 1938-39 (Box 7, Folder 420)
  - Weismiller, Edward, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 421)
  - Wenrich, John
    See: Oversize, Box 9, Folder 456
  - Wetstein, Aleen, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 422)
  - Wheelwright, John, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 423)
  - Williams, Oscar, 1938, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 424)
  - Williams, William Carlos, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 425)
  - Wing, Hugh Alan, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 426)
  - Wood, Charles Erskine Scott, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 427)
  - Zugsmith, Leane, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 428)
  - Unidentified manuscripts, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 429)
- Other Papers, 1929-69; Series III; 0.25; (1 box)
  Series III is arranged alphabetically by material type.
  - Advertisements, 1934, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 430)
  - Bills and receipts, 1934-69 (Box 8, Folder 431)
  - Copyright papers, 1941-43 (Box 8, Folder 432)
  - Photographs, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 433)
  - Press release, [1942] (Box 8, Folder 434)
  - Printed Works
    - Augusta Chronicle, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 435)
    - "Behind Bars" by Alex Comfort (Box 8, Folder 436)
    - The Bulletin Index
      See: Oversize, Box 9, Folder 453
    - Columbus, Ohio Dispatch, 1935 Mar 3 (Box 8, Folder 437)
    - Daily Oklahoman, 1935 Oct 27 (Box 8, Folder 438)
    - The Dying Muse by Earl Cuevas, 1935 (Box 8, Folder 439)
    - The Eminent Doctor Barnum Bunk by John E. Kake, 1929 (Box 8, Folder 440)
    - First Baptist Church, Pittsburgh, 1940-41 (Box 8, Folder 441)
    - Miscellaneous papers, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 442)
    - The New Day
      See: Oversize, Box 9, Folder 454
    - New Mexico Sentinel
      See: Oversize, Box 9, Folder 455
    - The New York Times
    - Pittsburgh Post Gazette, 1938 May 7 (Box 8, Folder 443)
    - Pittsburgh Press, 1942 Apr 17 (Box 8, Folder 444)
    - "The Poetic Viewpoint" [column], 1934-35 (Box 8, Folder 445)
    - The Ridgewood Herald [Paterson, N. J.?], 1935 Jul 12 (Box 8, Folder 446)
    - The Saturday Review, 1935 Dec 28 (Box 8, Folder 447)
    - Sewanee Review, 1938 Jan-Mar (Box 8, Folder 448)
    - Sunset Vogue, 1936 Mar 20 (Box 8, Folder 449)
    - United States. House of Representatives. Committee on Patents. Statement by Earl Cuevas, 1935 (Box 8, Folder 450)
    - Western Pennsylvania Poets: An Anthology, 1934-35, 1935 (Box 8, Folder 451)
  - Stationery, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 452)
- Oversize, 1934-38; 2; (1 box)
  Box 9 holds oversize materials from Series III.
  - The Bulletin Index [Pittsburgh, PA], 1934 Sep 13 (Box 9, Folder 453)
  - The New Day, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 454)
  - New Mexico Sentinel, 1937 (Box 9, Folder 455)
  - The New York Times, 1931 Aug 23 (Box 9, Folder 456)
- Restricted Fragile Papers, 2; (2 boxes)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Boxes 10-11: Restricted fragile material. Reference surrogates have been substituted in the main files. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
  Box 11 contains oversize material.
  - Box 1, folder 1 (Box 10, Folder 457)
  - Box 1, folder 5 (Box 10, Folder 458)
  - Box 1, folder 16 (Box 10, Folder 459)
  - Box 1, folder 28 (Box 10, Folder 460)
  - Box 1, folder 43 (Box 10, Folder 461)
  - Box 1, folder 49 (Box 10, Folder 462)
  - Box 1, folder 58 (Box 10, Folder 463)
  - Box 2, folder 69 (Box 10, Folder 464)
  - Box 2, folder 70 (Box 10, Folder 465)
  - Box 2, folder 102 (Box 10, Folder 466)
  - Box 2, folder 103 (Box 10, Folder 467)
  - Box 2, folder 108 (Box 10, Folder 468)
  - Box 2, folder 112 (Box 10, Folder 469)
  - Box 2, folder 122 (Box 10, Folder 470)
  - Box 2, folder 129 (Box 10, Folder 471)
  - Box 2, folder 132 (Box 10, Folder 472)
  - Box 2, folder 134 (Box 10, Folder 473)
  - Box 3, folder 137 (Box 10, Folder 474)
  - Box 3, folder 146 (Box 10, Folder 475)
  - Box 3, folder 178 (Box 10, Folder 476)
  - Box 3, folder 179 (Box 10, Folder 477)
  - Box 3, folder 180 (Box 10, Folder 478)
  - Box 3, folder 181 (Box 10, Folder 479)
  - Box 4, folder 234 (Box 10, Folder 480)
  - Box 4, folder 237 (Box 10, Folder 481)
  - Box 4, folder 241 (Box 10, Folder 482)
  - Box 5, folder 253 (Box 10, Folder 483)
  - Box 5, folder 256 (Box 10, Folder 484)
  - Box 5, folder 282 (Box 10, Folder 485)
  - Box 5, folder 286 (Box 10, Folder 486)
  - Box 5, folder 287 (Box 10, Folder 487)
  - Box 5, folder 289 (Box 10, Folder 488)
  - Box 5, folder 304 (Box 10, Folder 489)
  - Box 6, folder 313 (Box 10, Folder 490)
  - Box 6, folder 318 (Box 10, Folder 491)
  - Box 6, folder 323 (Box 10, Folder 492)
  - Box 6, folder 333 (Box 10, Folder 493)
  - Box 6, folder 343 (Box 10, Folder 494)
  - Box 6, folder 344 (Box 10, Folder 495)
  - Box 6, folder 354 (Box 10, Folder 496)
  - Box 6, folder 355 (Box 10, Folder 497)
  - Box 6, folder 363 (Box 10, Folder 498)
  - Box 7, folder 375 (Box 10, Folder 499)
  - Box 7, folder 388 (Box 10, Folder 500)
  - Box 7, folder 395 (Box 10, Folder 501)
  - Box 7, folder 406 (Box 10, Folder 502)
  - Box 7, folder 412 (Box 10, Folder 503)
  - Box 7, folder 417 (Box 10, Folder 504)
  - Box 7, folder 426 (Box 10, Folder 505)
  - Box 8, folder 435 (Box 10, Folder 506)
  - Box 8, folder 437 (Box 10, Folder 507)
  - Box 8, folder 438 (Box 10, Folder 508)
  - Box 8, folder 442 (Box 10, Folder 509)
  - Box 8, folder 443 (Box 10, Folder 510)
  - Box 8, folder 444 (Box 10, Folder 511)
  - Box 8, folder 445 (Box 10, Folder 512)
  - Box 8, folder 446 (Box 10, Folder 513)
  - Box 8, folder 449 (Box 10, Folder 514)
  - Box 9, folder 454 (Box 11, Folder 515)
  - Box 9, folder 455 (Box 11, Folder 516)
  - Box 9, folder 456 (Box 11, Folder 517)